Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004; 2; 613 items
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Mechanized Surfacing Force Chart, Undated (Map-tube 297)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000990
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; C.T.C. "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Vicinity of "LK" Cabin (Reproduction of 1960 Map), Undated (Map-tube 579)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000957
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; C.T.C. "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Vicinity of "TP" Cabin (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Undated (Map-tube 580)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000956
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; C.T.C. "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Vicinity of Bainbridge, NY (Reproduction of 1960 Map), Undated (Map-tube 578)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000958
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; C.T.C. "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Vicinity of Unadilla, NY (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Undated (Map-tube 577)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000961
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Main Street, Sidney (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Undated (Map-tube 556)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000969
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Wells Bridge, NY (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Map Number 550, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000964
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Wells Bridge, NY (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Map Number 551, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000963
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Wells Bridge, NY (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Map Number 552, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000962
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division; CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes Near "UA" and "UN" Cabins (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Undated (Map-tube 557)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000966
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania Division Jefferson Division; Carbondale to Jefferson Junction PA (Reproduction of 1937 Map), Undated (Map-tube 573)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000876
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania Division Nineveh Division; Jefferson Junction to Nineveh, NY (Reproduction of 1938 Map), Undated (Map-tube 572)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000877
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania Division Plymouth Branch; Straight Line Map Showing Car Capacity of Sidings (Reproduction of 1934 Map), Undated (Map-tube 570)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000879
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania Subdivision; Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between Mile Post A-190 and Mile Post A-177 (Reproduction of 1960 Map), Map Number 564, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000890
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania Subdivision; Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between Mile Post A-195 and Mile Post A-186 (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Map Number 562, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000883
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania-Susquehanna Division; CTC "QS" to "GR" Cutover Points in Unadilla, NY (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Undated (Map-tube 558)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000965
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania-Susquehanna Division; Mile Post A-178 to Mile Post A-172 in Carbondale, PA (Reproduction of 1959 Map), Map Number 561, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000886
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania-Susquehanna Division; Retirement of Portion of Coal Track in Schenevus, NY, 1956 (Map-tube 344)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001130
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania-Susquehanna Division; Track-Signal and Telephone Arrangement Between Mile Post A-1.57 and Mile Post A-144 (Reproduction of 1958 Map), Map Number 559, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000889
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania-Susquehanna Division; Track-Signal and Telephone Arrangement Between Signal 151.2 and Mile Post A-165 (Reproduction of 1958 Map), Map Number 560, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000888
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Pennsylvania-Susquehanna Division; Track-Signal and Telephone Arrangement Between Signal 160.2 and WC Cabin (Reproduction of 1958 Map), Map Number 563, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000885
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Proposed Track and Signal Changes from "YO" to "SA" in Albany, NY (Reproduction of 1963 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000950
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Proposed Track Changes at "GV" (Reproduction of 1963 Map), Map Number 474, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000955
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Proposed Track Changes at "GV" (Reproduction of 1963 Map), Map Number 475, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000943
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Real Estate and Industrial Department Map Showing Land at Carbondale (Reproduction of 1968 Map), Undated (Map-tube 544)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000899
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Rouses Point, NY (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Undated (Map-tube 555)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000971
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga and Champlain Subdivisions; Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between NG Cabin and Mile Post A-15 (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Map Number 568, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000946
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division "WX" to "JA", Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA000934, BLA000935, and BLA000940
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division, Piping Layout of Bridge and Building Department, Boarding Outfit (Reproduction of 1950 Map), Undated (Map-tube 255)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001135
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division, Sketch Showing Typical Concrete Mileposts Erected Under Approximate Numbers D-5484-85-86 & 87 (Reproduction of 1930 Map), Undated (Map-tube 281)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001121
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division: Preframed Members Proposed Motor Car Set-Off -131# Rail Standard (Reproduction of 1953), Undated (Map-tube 377)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001110
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; 16' Buda Crossing Gate Arm (Reproduction of 1935 Map), Undated (Map-tube 317)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001112
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; 16' Elliot Crossing Gate Arm (Reproduction of 1935 Map), Undated (Map-tube 303)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001113
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Details of Ice Box (Reproduction of 1943 Map), Undated (Map-tube 341)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001083
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Piping-Diesel Fuel Meter Box (Reproduction of 1952 Map), Undated (Map-tube 307)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001149
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Proposed Change of Track to Eliminate the Grade Crossings Through the City of Saratoga Springs, NY (Reproduction of 1931 Map), Undated (Map-tube 569)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Sketch of Standard Timber Rail Rack (Reproduction of 1931), Undated (Map-tube 350)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001107
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Straight Line Map Showing Car Capacity of Sidings in Ballston Spa, NY (Reproduction of 1951 Map), Map Number 466, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001326
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Straight Line Map Showing Car Capacity of Sidings in Mechanicville, NY (Reproduction of 1935 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000868
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Utilization of Relay Ties in Crossings (Reproduction of 1953 Map), Undated (Map-tube 295)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001108
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Subdivision; Operating Rules and Signal Aspect Changes Between Signal 4.1 and Signal 8.2 in Albany, NY (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000945
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga-Champlain Division, CTC "WX" to "JA", Track Changes and Cemetery Curve in West Waterford, NY (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Map Number 469, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000939
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga-Champlain Division, CTC "WX" to "JA", Track Changes between Pine Street and River Bridge No. 9.28 in Cohoes, NY (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Map Number 468, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000933
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga-Champlain Division, CTC "WX" to "JA", Track Changes, Vicinity M.P. A8 in Cohoes, NY (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Map Number 470, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000941
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga-Champlain Division; CTC "WX" to "JA"; Track Changes Vicinity of "JA" Cabin in Waterford Junction, NY (Reproduction of 1962 Map), Map Number 478, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000936
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga-Champlain Division; Sidetracks Serving Tougher Realty Corporation in Menands, NY (Reproduction of 1967), Map Number 481, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000944
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga-Susquehanna Subdivision; Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between M.P. S-7 and M.P. S-10 (Reproduction of 1965 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000930
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna and Saratoga Division; Yard Track Classification for Schenectady, Mohawk and Glenville, NY (Reproduction of 1923 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000871
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division Valuation Section 4, Details of Roof Truss in Shop Building No. 7 in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1949 Map), Undated (Map-tube 226)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000477
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division Valuation Section 4, Platforms, Catwalks and Ladders Installed on Boilers 211 and 346 in Oneonta, NY, 1947-1948 (Map-tube 245)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000472; Other Identification Number: 31-608
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Removal of No. 1 Track Pusher Switch, 1954 (Map-tube 296)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001152
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Addition of [Ladder to Lumber Wheel], Undated (Map-tube 433)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000495
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Automobile Unloading Platform in Worchester, NY, 1948 (Map-tube 368)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001157
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Bearing Brackets for BR 70.41, Undated (Map-tube 290)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001018
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Binghamton to Afton, NY (Reproduction of 1938 Map), Undated (Map-tube 574)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000880
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Car Repair Building at Glens Bridge, NY (Reproduction of 1930 Map), Undated (Map-tube 372)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001144
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Catwalks to Serve Valves Over Pumps and Tanks, Roundhouse Boiler Room in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1949 Map), Undated (Map-tube 448)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000458A-BLA000458B
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Details of Deck, N.B.M. Bridge 64.02 (Reproduction of 1934), Undated (Map-tube 387)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001153
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Details of Rail Top Culvert (Reproduction of 1947 Map), Undated (Map-tube 375)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000997
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Foundation Plan for New Boiler at Round House in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1947 Map), Undated (Map-tube 434)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000471
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Grilllages for Bridge 66.31 (Reproduction of 1940 Map), Undated (Map-tube 309)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000973
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Jacket for North Abutment Bridge 66.31 (Reproduction 1948), Undated (Map-tube 306)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000975
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Location of Boiler Installed in Enginehouse, 1948 (Map-tube 435)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000468
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Locker Room To Be Installed Second Floor of Roundhouse in Binghamton, NY, 1952 (Map-tube 294)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000994; Other Identification Number: SQ-39-857
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Motor Car Connecting Rods In Use On Susquehanna Division (Reproduction of 1935 Map), Undated (Map-tube 380)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001027
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Plan for Preframing Deck of Turntable at Oneonta, NY, 1945 (Map-tube 384)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001147
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Plan for Preframing Deck Ties for Turntable in Cooperstown, NY, 1951 (Map-tube 298)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001151
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Plan for Preframing Decks of South and North Bound Tracks of Bridge 70.41 (Reproduction of 1949 Map), Undated (Map-tube 293)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001014
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Plan, Elevations, and Details for New Boiler at Round House in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1947 Map), Undated (Map-tube 446)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000470
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Plans for Preframing Deck of Bridge T2 61.83, 1943 (Map-tube 366)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001011
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Plans for Preframing Decks of N.B. Bridge 76.28, 1943 (Map-tube 318)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000999
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Rearrangement of Tracks at "DA" Cabin, 1941 (Map-tube 383)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001145; Other Identification Number: SQ-52-49
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Repairs to Bottom Flanges Girders of Bridge 78.92 (Reproduction of 1949), Undated (Map-tube 385)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001008
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Side Track To Serve GLF in Schenevus, NY, 1946 (Map-tube 308)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001024
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Stairways to be Installed on Lumber and Wheel Cranes in Oneonta, NY, Undated (Map-tube 445)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000494
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Straight Line Map Showing Car Capacity of Sidings, Binghamton, NY (Reproduction of 1934 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000867
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Track and Signal Arrangement of NG Cabin to Signal 14.2 North of West Waterford, NY (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Undated (Map-tube 576)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000942
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Track and Signal Arrangement of NG Cabin to WX Cabin (Reproduction of 1962), Map Number 480, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000938
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between Mile Post A-106 and Mile Post A-95 (Reproduction of 1961 Map), Map Number 482, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000952
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between Mile Post A-117 and Sidney Station, Map Number 483, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000953
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between Mile Post A-204 and Mile Post A-194 (Reproduction of 1960 Map), Map Number 566, Undated (Flat-file 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000891
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad with Corporate "Tilte" and Lengths (Reproduction of 1928 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000905
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Best Crossing 1.25 Miles East of Whitehall, NY, Map Number 473, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001279
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: New York Power and Light Corporation Distribution Permit (Reproduction of 1941 Map), Map Number 472, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001031
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Site and Services, Non-Standard Railroad Clearances (Reproduction of 1969 Map), Map Number 492, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001357
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Site and Services, Railroad Construction Details (Reproduction of 1969), Map Number 491, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001356
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Site and Services, Surfaces Facility Sheet No. 2 (Reproduction of 1968 Map), Map Number 489, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001354
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Site and Services, Surfaces Facility Sheet No. 4 (Reproduction of 1968 Map), Map Number 488, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001353
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Site and Services, Woodyard Surfacing Details and X-Sections (Reproduction of 1969 Map), Map Number 490, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001355
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Susquehanna Division; General Plan for Signal Bridge in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1938), Map Number 487, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000295
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Susquehanna Division; Plan for Prefaming Deck Bridge 64.02, 1952 (Map-tube 340)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001155
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Champlain Division Yard Map, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000947
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Corridor and Other Profiles, 1978; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA000910, BLA000909, BLA000912, BLA000911, and BLA001400
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Existing Trackage from Scranton to Buttonwood (Reproduction of 1981 Map), Map Number 467, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000923
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Northeast Rail Lines, 1981 (Map-tube 455)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000484B
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Present and Proposed Corridor Routes, Comparative Profiles, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000908
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Proprietary Lines Map, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000913
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Rail Lines and Facilities of Operational Interest in the Northeast (Reproduction of 1978 Map), Undated (Map-tube 359)
    Original .Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000978
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Rail Lines and Facilities of Operational Interest in the Northeast (Reproduction of 1978), Undated (Map-tube 343)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000977
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Rail Service Area (Reproduction of 1978 Map), Undated (Map-tube 414)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000515
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Rail Service Area Maps, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA000914 and BLA000915
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Roundhouse Rouses Point, NY (Reproduction of 1981 Map), Undated (Map-tube 398)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001392
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Saratoga Subdivision; Area in Vicinity of 25th Street Crossing in Watervliet, NY (Reproduction of 1983 Map), Map Number 471, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001341
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Schematic Showing Proposed Track Arrangement "BD" to "SA" in Connection with the 188/181 Connector in Binghamton, NY (Reproduction of 1982 Map), Map Number 549, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000920
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Skylight Window Sash for Oneonta Round House Blueprint (Reproduction of 1950 Map), Undated (Map-tube 265)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000464
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Susquehanna Division Track Maps, 1973; 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA000916, BLA000924, and BLA000925